<resources>
    <string name="title_app_name">TrainingTracker</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_status">Status</string>
    <string name="title_setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="title_one_rep_max">One Rep Max</string>

    <string name="event">event</string>
    <string name="general_deletion_warning">Are you sure you want to delete this item?</string>

    <!--    exercise    -->
    <string name="event_log">log</string>
    <!--    <string name="event_add_log">add log</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="event_delete_log">delete log</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="event_edit_log">edit log</string>-->
    <string name="exercise_add">Add a new exercise</string>
    <string name="exercise_enter_weight">Enter weight</string>
    <string name="exercise_enter_rep">Enter reps</string>
    <string name="exercise_deletion_warning">All records will be deleted. Once deleted, they cannot be recovered. </string>

    <string name="event_set">set</string>
    <string name="event_add_set">add set</string>

    <!--    tag    -->
    <string name="event_tag">tag</string>
    <string name="event_add_tag">add tag</string>
    <string name="event_delete_tag">delete tag</string>
    <string name="event_edit_tag">edit tag</string>
    <string name="event_click_tag">click tag</string>
    <string name="tag_enter_name">Enter a tag name</string>
    <string name="tag_deletion_warning">All records will be deleted. Once deleted, they cannot be recovered.</string>

    <!--    muscle    -->
    <string name="event_muscle">muscle</string>
    <!--    <string name="event_add_muscle">add muscle</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="event_delete_muscle">delete muscle</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="event_edit_muscle">edit muscle</string>-->
    <string name="muscle_select">Select muscle</string>
    <string name="discard_set_count">discard set count</string>
    <string name="one_rep_max_pb">ONE REP MAX(PB)</string>


    <string name="terms_and_conditions_html">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Terms and Conditions</b><br/><br/>
        <b>1. Introduction</b><br/>
        Welcome to our Gym Training Tracker app ("App"). This App is designed to help you monitor and improve your fitness regimen by providing tools to track your workouts, achievements, and personal records. By using our App, you agree to these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy, which cover your access and use of our services.<br/><br/>
        <b>2. User Consent</b><br/>
        By registering an account and utilizing the App, you explicitly consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your data as described in these Terms and Conditions and our detailed Privacy Policy.<br/><br/>
        <b>3. Data Collection</b><br/>
        To provide and enhance our services, we collect several types of data, including:<br/>
        — Personal Data: This may include your name, contact details (such as email), age, and other personal information.<br/>
        — Performance Data: Data related to your workout sessions, including types of exercises, repetitions, and personal fitness records.<br/>
        — Diagnostic Data: When you report an issue, we collect necessary data to diagnose and resolve problems, which may include system logs and detailed app usage information.<br/><br/>
        <b>4. Purpose of Data Collection</b><br/>
        Your data is vital for the following purposes:<br/>
        — Enhancing App Functionality: To provide a personalized and efficient user experience.<br/>
        — Resolving Issues: To quickly address and rectify any problems reported through the App.<br/>
        — Customizing User Experience: To adapt and suggest workouts that align with your fitness goals.<br/><br/>
        <b>5. Data Use</b><br/>
        The data collected is essential for the operation and management of our App, including for troubleshooting, improvements, and maintaining user records as part of our service offering.<br/><br/>
        <b>6. Data Sharing and Disclosure</b><br/>
        Your personal data is not shared with any third parties, except under these circumstances:<br/>
        — Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including server hosting and analytics, under strict confidentiality obligations.<br/>
        — Legal Requirements: If required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, we may disclose your information as necessary.<br/><br/>
        <b>7. Data Retention and Deletion</b><br/>
        We retain diagnostic data only as long as necessary to resolve the issues for which it was collected. Subsequently, this data is securely deleted. You can request the deletion of your personal data or account by contacting our support team.<br/><br/>
        <b>8. User Rights</b><br/>
        Under the UK GDPR, you are afforded specific rights, which include:<br/>
        — Access and Correction: You can access and update your data at any time via the App settings.<br/>
        — Withdrawal of Consent: You can withdraw your consent for future processing at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.<br/>
        — Data Portability: You may request a copy of your data in a standard electronic format.<br/><br/>
        <b>9. Security Measures</b><br/>
        We implement robust security measures to protect your data against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These include encryption, firewalls, and secure server facilities.<br/><br/>
        <b>10. Changes to the Terms</b><br/>
        We reserve the right to modify these terms at any time. Should any significant changes occur, we will notify you via the App or through email.<br/><br/>
        <b>11. Contact Information</b><br/>
        For any inquiries related to these Terms and Conditions or your personal data, please contact us at: trainingtrackermailbox@gmail.com.<br/><br/>
        <b>12. Governing Law</b><br/>
        These Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the United Kingdom and are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the United Kingdom.<br/><br/>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="feedback_mail">trainingtrackermailbox@gmail.com</string>

</resources>